<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ProtectFromBullying</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_reports">Reports</string>
    <string name="title_kids">Your Kids</string>
    <string name="title_information">Information</string>

    <string name="wholestory_1">Take the cyberbullying seriously.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_2">Help them identify what cyberbullying is.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_3">Find out details about the cyberbullying.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_4">Teach them that cyberbullying is never ok.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_5">Reassure them that they are loved.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_6">Work together to figure out ways they can take back power from the ‘bully’.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_7">Involve them in decision making at home to increase their sense of power and control.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_8">Be a role model by calmly managing your own emotions.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_9">Create opportunities to expand their support friendships.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_10">Support them to speak to another trusted adult or counsellor.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_11">Advise them to avoid opening emails, messages or responding to cyberbullies.</string>
    <string name="wholestory_12">Respect that they may not want to limit online access as this can seem like a punishment and lead to greater social isolation.</string>

    <string name="takeaction_1">Notifying the school of the cyberbullying.</string>
    <string name="takeaction_2">Find out more about the school’s anti-bullying policies.</string>
    <string name="takeaction_3">Help them to keep a record of the bullying in case it needs to be reported.</string>
    <string name="takeaction_4">Reporting serious cases of cyberbullying to the Police - cyber stalking, which is repeated harassment usually containing threatening messages with the aim to intimidate and create fear, is a crime and should always be reported.</string>
    <string name="takeaction_5">Help your child to “call out” the behaviour of the ‘bully’.</string>
    <string name="takeaction_6">Encourage them to use statements like “You are going too far – this is bullying and I want you to stop”.</string>
    <string name="takeaction_7">Suggest your child ‘block’ or remove the bully from their friend list and change their username or mobile number.</string>
    <string name="takeaction_8">Help them file a complaint with the website manager.</string>
    <string name="takeaction_9">Help them spend some time away from the computer and mobile phone by increasing their options for doing other fun activities.</string>
    <string name="takeaction_10">Follow up after your child tries a solution to see how it went.</string>

    <string name="waystotackle_11">Focus on identifying a solution with your child. Your attitude will influence your child. A confident, positive and resilient attitude can help to stop bullying from continuing</string>
    <string name="waystotackle_22">Fighting with the other child (as distinct from defending themselves from a physical attack) can escalate the situation, and your child may be reprimanded for their part in a fight.</string>
    <string name="waystotackle_33">Ignoring the person doing the bullying, telling them to stop and then walking away, pretending you dont care; act unimpressed or not bothered, go somewhere safe.</string>
    <string name="waystotackle_44">Not to respond to the message or image, save the evidence, block or delete the sender, report the situation to the Internet Service Provider or phone service provider; they can help you block messages or calls.</string>
    <string name="waystotackle_55">Encourage your child to talk to the teacher or other staff, e.g. school guidance officer. Let them know that you will also report it to the school if the bullying doesnt stop after your child tries the strategies</string>
    <string name="waystotackle_66">Discuss with the school ways to help your child (and other students) to learn about problem solving, conflict resolution, social skills, developing resilience, dealing with strong emotions, handling difficult situations and people.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_your_kids">YourKidsActivity</string>

    <string name="addkidsprocedure1">* Enter the first name of your kid.</string>
    <string name="addkidsprocedure2">* Click on "Generate" to generate the QR code.</string>
    <string name="addkidsprocedure3">* The QR code contains the kid name and a unique identifier.</string>
    <string name="addkidsprocedure4">* Scan the QR code in your kids phone once the app is installed.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_kid_home">KidHomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_kid_bar_code_scan">KidBarCodeScanActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_kid_qrscan">KidQRScanActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard">DashboardActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard_charts">DashboardChartsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard_your_kids">DashboardYourKidsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cyber_bully_texts">CyberBullyTextsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bully_identities">BullyIdentitiesActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bully_identities_your_kids">BullyIdentitiesYourKidsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_take_action">TakeActionActivity</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_counselling">CounsellingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_general_legal_information">GeneralLegalInformationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_youth_law">YouthLawActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_psychological_help">PsychologicalHelpActivity</string>


</resources>
